Guide to the Richard Pollay. Tobacco industry promotion (TIPS) collection, 1885-2012 and undated RL.11612
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 8000. Litigation and Court Records, 1929-2005; undated; 11
  - 8052. Schwarz v. Philip Morris, 1952-2001; 154
    - Contents of binder 2, 1973-2001; 3 folders (Box 107)
      Includes materials from Philip Morris Document Site; depositions of Richard Schwarz, Paul Schwarz, Shirley Chuck-Dye
    - Contents of binder 3, 1954-2001; 2 folders (Box 107)
      Includes correspondence; cigarette advertising; Pollay writings; trial materials; trial exhibits
  - 8053. Toy Trial Group (Delaware; asbestos litigation), 1950-1997; 155
    - Contents of binder 1, 1950-1997 (Box 107)
      Includes correspondence; defendants' exhibits
    - Contents of binder 2, 1964-1997 (Box 107)
      Includes defendants' exhibits; depositions materials; correspondence
  - 8054. J.T.I. MacDonald, et al v. Attorney General of Canada, 1980-2003; 156
    - Anne Lavack (University of Winnipeg)--Literature on warning labels (abstracts and citations), 2001 (Box 107)
    - Anne Lavack (University of Winnipeg)--Marketing Objectives and Tools: Inside the Tobacco Industry, 2000 (Box 107)
    - Anne Lavack (University of Winnipeg)--Marketing of Tobacco Products: A Review of the Academic Literature 1993-1996, 1997 (Box 107)
    - Anne Lavack (University of Winnipeg)--Tobacco Company Corporate Documents: A Review and Summary, 1997 (Box 107)
    - Contents of binder--Anne Lavack, 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 107)
      The Guildford Documents Highlights Report (British-American Tobacco Co.); Tobacco Company Corporate Documents: A Review and Summary; Summary of Corporate Documents from RJR-MacDonald
    - Contents of binder--Ed Ricard (Imperial Tobacco) examination, 2002 (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Expert witnesses, 2000; 2 folders (Box 108)
      Expert reports from Adrian Wilkinson (psychologist in private practice), Michael Waterson (World Advertising Research Center), Lucy Henke (University of Louisiana, Lafayette), Rafe Engle (lawyer), Gerald Wilde (emeritus, Queen's University), Roderick Power (emeritus, Macquarie University)
    - Contents of binder--Michael Waterson examination, 2002; 2 folders (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Michael Waterson references 1-20, 1982-2001; 3 folders (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Michael Waterson references 21-26, 1993-2000; 3 folders (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Richard Pollay writings, 1995-2002; 4 folders (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Superior Court decision (English and French), 2002; 2 folders (Box 108)
    - Contents of binder--Supporting materials for the defense, 1993-2000; 3 folders (Box 108)
      Includes articles, scholarly reports, expert report of Zalman Amit (Concordia University)
    - Ed Ricard testimony, 2001; 2 folders (Box OV5)
    - John Pierce expert report, 2000 (Box OV5)
    - News items and miscellaneous, 1993-2002 (Box 108)
    - Richard Pollay--Contracts, correspondence, etc., 1997-2003; 2 folders (Box 108)
    - Rob Parker (Canadian Tobacco Manufacturers' Council--CMTC) speech to Calgary Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 108)
    - Supporting documents for plaintiffs, etc., 1980-2002; 2 folders (Box 108)
      Includes Robert Heath, Hidden power of advertising; journal articles; Admap bibliographies
    - Tobacco Act (Chapter 13) and related documents, 1999-2000 (Box 108)
    - Witness testimonies--Andre Castonguay, Richard Pollay, 2002; 3 folders (Box 109)
  - 8055. Oliver and Dates v. R.J. Reynolds, et al ("Lights" case), 1972-2000; undated; 157
    - Class action complaint, undated (Box 109)
    - "Lights" documents, 1972-2000; 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Pollay documents, 1998-2000 (Box 109)
      Includes affidavit, writings, articles by others, correspondence
  - 8056. Group Health Plan v. Philip Morris, et al, 2000-2001; 158
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2000-2001 (Box 109)
    - Pollay expert report, 2000; 2 folders (Box 109)
  - 8057. Miscellaneous Litigation and Consulting, 1996-2001; 159
    - Folder A. Arch v. American Tobacco Company, et al, 1997 (Box 109)
    - Folder B. Asbestos Workers Medical Fund v. Philip Morris, et al, 1998-1999 (Box 109)
    - Folder C. British Columbia (BC) Tobacco Damages Recovery Act, 1997-2001 (Box 109)
    - Folder D. State of California v. R.J. Reynolds, 1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder E. State of California v. Philip Morris, et al, 1994-2001 (Box 109)
    - Folder F. Hall v. Philip Morris, et al, 1997 (Box 109)
    - Folder G. Insolia v. Philip Morris, 1997 (Box 109)
    - Folder H. King County (Washington) Board of Health, 1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder I. Mangini v. R.J. Reynolds, 1997 (Box 109)
    - Folder J. State of Maryland v. Philip Morris, et al, 1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder K. State of Missouri v. American Tobacco Company, et al, 1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder L. Neri v. R.J. Reynolds, 1999 (Box 109)
    - Folder M. Nixon v. Philip Morris, 1999 (Box 109)
    - Folder N. Pennsylvania Tobacco Litigation, 1997-1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder O. Scott litigation, 2000 (Box 109)
    - Folder P. State of Washington v. American Tobacco Company, et al, 1996-1998 (Box 109)
    - Folder Q. West Virginia mass litigation, 1997-2000 (Box 109)
    - Folder R. Wisconsin v. Philip Morris, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 109)
  - 8058. Caputo, et al v. Imperial Tobacco, et al (Toronto), 1951-2002; 160
    - Andreas Seibert--Exhibits for affidavit, 1951-2001; 3 folders (Box 109)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995-2002 (Box 109)
    - Richard Pollay--Affidavit with exhibits (4 vols.), 2002; 5 folders (Box 109)
    - Richard Pollay--Affidavit with exhibits (4 vols.), 2002; 7 folders (Box 110)
    - Ronald Faber (University of Minnesota)--Affidavit and cross-examination, 2000; 4 folders (Box 110)
    - Tobacco industry advertising reports, 1998-2002 (Box 110)
      Includes Physicians for a Smoke-Free Canada report on advertising expenditures 1987-1998; FTC cigarette reports; Imperial Tobacco annual information
  - 8059. Miles v. Philip Morris (Illinois), 2003; 161
    - Background and media on case, 2003 (Box 110)
    - Joel Cohen (University of Florida)-Transcript of testimony, 2003; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Trial judgment, 2003 (Box 110)
  - 8060. Betty Bullock v. Philip Morris, et al (California), 2002; 162
    - Marvin Goldberg (Penn State) testimony, 2002; 4 folders (Box 110)
  - 8061. Brown, et al v. American Tobacco Company, et al (California), 2001-2002; undated; 163
    - Complaint, 2001 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2001-2002 (Box 110)
    - Jeffrey Arnett (University of Maryland) articles on adolescent smoking and cigarette advertisements, 2001 (Box 110)
    - Substantive reach of California's Unfair Business Practices Act, undated (Box 110)
  - 8062. Reller v. Philip Morris, et al (California), 1954-2003; undated; 164
    - Additional reliance documents referred to in correspondence, 1955-2003; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - American Tobacco Company documents, press releases (includes database search results), 1954-2003 (Box 110)
    - Complaint, 2001 (Box 110)
    - Contents of compilation reels created by the History of Advertising Archives, 2002 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2003; undated (Box 110)
    - Law Offices of Michael J. Puize (attorney for plaintiff) press package, undated (Box 110)
    - List of defense expert witnesses, 2003 (Box 110)
    - Motion to exclude Richard Pollay testimony and Pollay response, 2003 (Box 110)
    - Plaintiff exhibit 134/Deposition exhibit 1: Pall Mall Course of Action, 1958 (Box OV5)
    - Plaintiff exhibit 135: Trends in public attitudes on the possibility of a health hazard in cigarette smoking, 1959 (Box OV5)
    - Plaintiff exhibit 136: Significance of the Survey Findings to Pall Mall Famous Cigarettes, circa 1960 (Box OV5)
    - Print advertisements relating to case, 1950s-1970s (Box 110)
    - Print advertisements relating to case, 1952-1956 (Box OV1)
      Includes Camel, Chesterfield, Pall Mall, Philip Morris
    - Richard Pollay--Deposition, 2003; 2 folders (Box 110)
    - Richard Pollay--Opposition to defendant motion for summary judgment, 2003 (Box 111)
    - Richard Pollay--Testimony, 2003; 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Richard Pollay--Writings on the tobacco industry, 1990-2002 (Box 111)
    - Reller smoking history; chronologies and trade notes on various cigarette brands, 2003 (Box 111)
  - 8064. Clara Gault Freeman v. Brown & Williamson (Georgia), 1946-2004; undated; 165
    - Contents of binder--Documents 1, 1968-1993; undated; 3 folders (Box 111)
      Index at beginning of binder
    - Contents of binder--Documents 2, 1968-1993; undated; 3 folders (Box 111)
    - Contents of binder--Documents 3, 1968-1993; undated; 2 folders (Box 111)
    - Contents of binder--Journal articles, 1987-2002; 2 folders (Box 111)
    - Contents of binder--Kool advertising in Ebony and Jet, 1970s-1990s; 2 folders (Box 111)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 1, 1946-1992; undated; 3 folders (Box 111)
      "Selected documents found on B&W Collection of Tobacco Documents Online." Index at beginning of binder
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 2, 1946-1992; undated; 4 folders (Box 111)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 3, 1946-1992; undated; 4 folders (Box 112)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 4, 1946-1992; undated; 5 folders (Box 112)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 5, 1946-1992; undated; 5 folders (Box 112)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 6, 1946-1992; undated; 6 folders (Box 112)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 7, 1946-1992; undated; 3 folders (Box 112)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 7, 1946-1992; undated (Box 113)
    - Contents of binder--Notebook 8, 1946-1992; undated; 2 folders (Box 113)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2003-2004 (Box 113)
    - Expert witnesses, 2003; undated (Box 113)
      Includes statement of Alvin Williams (University of Southern Mississippi)
    - Resource file--Kool cigarettes, 1957-2003 (Box 113)
    - Resource file--"Light" cigarettes, 2001 (Box 113)
    - Resource file--Menthol, 2000-2003 (Box 113)
    - Resource file--Miscellaneous, 1976-2003 (Box 113)
    - Resource file--Race and ethnicity, 1992-2003 (Box 113)
    - Resource file--Smoker Personality Study, 1980s (Box 113)
    - Resource file--Youth and smoking, 1994-1995 (Box 113)
    - Richard Pollay file (expert witness materials), 2003 (Box 113)
  - 8065. United States of America v. Philip Morris, et al, 1999-2005; undated; 166
    - Contents of binder--4004. U.S. Department of Justice litigation, 1999-2003 (Box 113)
      Includes "Tobacco industry statements in the US Department of Justice lawsuit" prepared for Rep. Waxman; U.S. vs. Philip Morris, et al Complaint for Damages and Appendix to Complaint
    - Folder 1. U.S. response to joint defendants' preliminary proposed findings of fact and conclusions of law regarding affirmative defenses, 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 2. Role of slotting fees and trade promotions in shaping how tobacco is marketed in retail stores (Paul Bloom, University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 3. Expert testimony of Dr. Michael Eriksen (CDC), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 4. Expert report of Frank J. Chaloupka (University of Illinois-Chicago), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 5. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp.i to 180 (sect. I), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 6. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 181-211 (sect. II-III), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 7. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 212-354 (sect. IV.A), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 8. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 355-568 (sect. IV.B-IV.D), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 9. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 569-795 (sect. IV.E), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 10. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 796-981 (sect. IV.F-IV.G), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 11. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact pp. 982-1149 (sect. V-IX), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 12. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact Appendix pp. 1-211, 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 13. U.S. preliminary proposed findings of fact: Annotations, 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 14. Written direct examination of Robert J. Dolan (University of Michigan), 2003 (Box 113)
    - Folder 15. Written direct examination of Dean Krugman (University of Georgia), 2003 (Box 114)
    - Joint defendants' final proposed pre-trial findings of fact and conclusions of law executive summary, 2004 (Box 114)
    - News items and miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 114)
    - United States' final proposed findings of fact--Table of contents, executive summary, undated (Box 114)
    - Written direct examination of James Heckman (University of Chicago), undated (Box 114)
  - 8066. British American Tobacco, et al v. Secretary of State for Health (Great Britain; point of sale litigation), 2002-2004; undated; 167
    - Book of pleadings (plenary summons, statement of claim), 2004 (Box 114)
      Includes judicial review claim form; detailed statement of grounds; suggested reading list; witness statement of Timothy Geoffrey Fraser Lord (Tobacco Manufacturers Association); witness statement of Andrew William Brown (Advertising Association); first witness statement of Frederic Gaiddon (Altadis/SEITA)
    - Contents of binder--Vol. 1, 2004 (Box 114)
      Includes exhibit list; second witness statement of Timothy Geoffrey Fraser Lord (Tobacco Manufacturers Association); witness statement of Barrie Gunter (University of Sheffield); witness statement of Jean Jules Boddewyn (CUNY)
    - Contents of binder--Vol. 2, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Judgment, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--Curriculum vitae, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--How Cigarette Advertising Works: Rich Imagery and Poor Information, 2002 (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--Point of Purchase Advertising of Tobacco Expert Report (Draft), undated (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--Second statement, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--Witness statement 3rd draft, 2004 (Box 114)
    - Richard Pollay--Witness statement final draft, 2004 (Box 114)
  - 8999. Tobacco Litigation-Related Print Materials, 1960s-2001; 168
    - 8999.1. Contents of binder--Tobacco on Trial 1, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 114)
      Index to articles at beginning of binder
    - 8999.1. Contents of binder--Tobacco on Trial 2, 1990-1994; 2 folders (Box 114)
    - 8999.1. Contents of binder--Tobacco on Trial 3, 1995 (Box 114)
    - 8999.2. Contents of binder--Tobacco Litigation '98: The Burning Issues, 1998; 4 folders (Box 114)
      Includes Andrews Tobacco Industry Litigation Reporter; attendee and speaker lists; Brian Campf--Class actions by smokers: Recent activity in the certified class actions; E. Ralph Walker--Defective cigarette design: What is it and how do you prove it?; I. Alan Feingold, et al--Presenting the medical expert in a lung cancer case: A trial demonstration; Harry Potter and Thomas Gilde--Health care cost recovery actions: The Texas and Minnesota cases revisited; Vincent Miller--Using statistics to measure tobacco-related health care costs; Steve Berman--Privilege issues in tobacco litigation; John Broaddus--Recent developments in the Union Trust Fund litigation; Gregory Leyh et al--The impact of the proposed Tobacco Product Liability Act of 1998 on individual cases, class actions, health care cost recovery actions, and the public health community; Richard Pollay--Dirty tricks and sly tactics: On misleading cigarette advertising and public relations; Patrick Coughlin--Consumer fraud claims: An analysis of what has worked in various states and other countries; Carolyn Dressler et al--Presenting the nicotine addiction expert: A trial demonstration; Kenneth McClain--Revelations from the Liggett documents
    - 8999.3. Contents of binder--Affidavits and Opinions I, 1987-2001; 2 folders (Box 114)
      Table of contents at beginning of binder
    - 8999.3. Contents of binder--Affidavits and Opinions II, 1987-2001; 2 folders (Box 114)
    - 8999.4. Contents of binder--"Aces" miscellaneous information for trials #1, 1960s-2000; 2 folders (Box 114)
    - 8999.4. Contents of binder--"Aces" miscellaneous information for trials #2, 1960s-2000; 2 folders (Box 115)
- 9000. Special Topics, 1919-2002; undated; 12
  - 9001. Tobacco and Youth--United States, 1986-2002; 169
    - Adolescent Smoking: Research and Health Policy (Paul Cleary et al), 1986 (Box 115)
    - ASSIST (American Stop Smoking Intervention Study for Cancer Prevention) resource packet, 1999 (Box 115)
    - Campaign for Tobacco-Free Kids print advertisement, 1997 (Box 115)
    - Contents of binder--Kids Can Trash Tobacco Advertising conference, 1996 (Box 115)
    - Contents of binder--Operation Storefront: Youth Against Tobacco Advertising and Promotion, phase II, 1996 (Box 115)
    - People of the State of California v. R.J. Reynolds, statement of decision, 2002 (Box 115)
    - Tobacco and Youth Reporter, 1988 Autumn (Box OV1)
    - Tobacco Free Youth: How to Reduce Sales to Minors in Your Community, 1992 (Box 115)
    - Youth Tobacco Surveillance--United States, 2000, 2001 (Box 115)
  - 9002. Tobacco and Youth--Canada, 1988-1998; 170
    - Beauty from the Inside Out: A Smoking Prevention Workshop for Adolescent Girls facilitator guide, 1994 (Box 115)
    - Contents of binder--Healthy Canada Heart Smart Kids resource packet, 1995; 3 folders (Box 115)
    - Smoke-Free educational resource kit for educators of children ages 3 to 6, 1988 (Box 115)
      Cassette tape (RL11612-CAS-023) removed to Audiovisual Materials
    - Smoke-Free Class of 2000 grade 7 module, 1994 (Box 115)
    - Tobacco Or Kids materials, 1998 (Box 115)
    - Youth and Tobacco Fact Sheets, 1993-1995 (Box 115)
    - Youth Smoking Survey, 1994 (Box 115)
  - 9005. Innovations in Youth Tobacco Control, 2002; 171
    - Contents of binder--Conference materials, 2002; 2 folders (Box 115)
      Video (RL11612-VHS-343) removed to Audiovisual Materials
  - 9501. Tobacco and Women, 1969-1995; 172
    - Contents of binder--Targeting Women, 1969-1989; 2 folders (Box 115)
      Includes Hal Weinstein: How an agency builds a brand--The Virginia Slims story; Katherine Jones: Women's brands--Cigarette advertising explicitly directed toward women; R.J. Reynolds Dakota cigarette documents
    - Dakota cigarette marketing materials, 1989-2000 (Box 115)
    - National Workshop on Women and Tobacco (Canada), 1988 (Box 115)
    - Women and Tobacco: A Framework for Action (Canada), 1995 (Box 115)
    - Women and Tobacco: Second National Workshop (Canada), 1995 (Box 115)
  - 9801. Tobacco and Events, 1995; 173
    - Contents of binder--Sports, 1995 (Box 115)
  - 9803. Tobacco and Sponsorships, circa 1998; 174
    - What is the purpose of tobacco industry sponsorships?, circa 1998 (Box 115)
  - 9900. General Tobacco-Related Materials, 1919-2000; undated; 175
    - 9901.1. Such Popularity Must Be Deserved: The Advertising of Chesterfield and Marlboro Cigarettes 1924-1969, 1992 (Box 115)
      Jennifer Herndon Master's thesis, UNC-CH
    - 9901.2. Oligopolistic Competition and Cigarette Advertising 1946-1965, 1968; 3 folders (Box 115)
      Noel Zabriskie doctoral dissertation, University of Illinois
    - 9901.3. An Evaluation of the Effects of Socially Induced Stress on Cigarette Smoking, 1983 (Box 115)
      Peter Illich Master's thesis, Concordia University
    - 9901.4. The Political Dynamics of Regulating Advertising in Malaysia: A Case Study of Cigarette Advertising, 1996; 2 folders (Box 116)
      Teck-Hua Ngu doctoral dissertation, Penn State
    - 9904. Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Conference materials, 1997 (Box 116)
    - 9905. Tobacco Industry Sponsorship in the United States, 1995-1999 (Michael Siegel, Boston University), 2000 (Box 116)
    - 9906. Museum and library collections, undated (Box 116)
      Includes brochures from Duke University, Cummings Center for Advertising Studies, Marlboro Advertising History Collection
    - 9907. Smoking celebrities lists, undated; 2 folders (Box 116)
    - 9907. Tobacco: Does it really hurt me? (in Physical Culture, June issue), 1919 (Box 116)
    - 9907. Tobacco Hall of Shame (Roswell Park Cancer Institute), 1991 (Box 116)
- Ephemera (Tobacciana), 1894-2002; undated; 13
  - Apparel, undated; 176
    - Alpine Lights--Rain cap, "It's a whole new Alpine", undated (Box E1)
    - Camel--Apron, Joe Camel "What's Cookin'?", undated (Box E1)
    - Camel--Joe Camel boxer shorts, undated (Box E1)
    - Camel--Joe Camel gym shorts, undated (Box E1)
    - Camel--Sandal, Club Camel, undated (Box E1)
      "Camel" letters in reverse on sole so it prints brand name in the sand
    - Camel--Scarf, undated (Box E1)
    - Dakota Lights--Bandana, undated (Box E1)
    - Dakota Lights--String tie, clasp has Dakota logo, undated (Box E1)
    - Peter Jackson--Bib (for competition) for Peter Jackson Tour, undated (Box E1)
    - Winston--Trousers, undated (Box E1)
      Drawstring trousers printed with Winston logo, "How good it is" slogan
  - Apparel--Hats, 1989-1992; undated; 177
    - Basic--Your Basic Hat, black, undated (Box E2)
    - Beech-Nut--Beech-Nut Choice Tobacco Leaf Chewing Tobacco, blue and white, undated (Box E2)
    - Buz--Catch a Buz 604/688-2735, Black, undated (Box E2)
    - Cambridge--Black and red, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Club Camel, blue and white, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Camel GT, G.I. Joe's Grand Prix, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Joe Camel billiards, purple and teal, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Camel Powered, Smokin' Joe's Racing, purple and gold doo-rag style, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Retro script, blue, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Smooth Character, blue corduroy, undated (Box E2)
    - Camel--Smooth Character, blue acid wash, undated (Box E2)
    - Chattanooga Chew--Easygoing flavor born in the south, white/yellow/black, undated (Box E2)
    - Cigar Afficionado--Black, undated (Box E2)
    - Copenhagen--Copenhagen Snuff, red and white, undated (Box E2)
    - Copenhagen--Copenhagen Snuff United States Tobacco Co., gray/black/maroon, undated (Box E2)
    - Export "A"--White, undated (Box E2)
    - Export "A"--Salmon Showdown, green and tan, undated (Box E2)
    - John Player--John Player Special racing, black, undated (Box E2)
    - Kool--"K", green and black, undated (Box E2)
    - Kool--Race car, green and tan, undated (Box E2)
    - Kool--White plastic visor, undated (Box E2)
    - Levi Garrett--The Hunter's Choice, camouflage, undated (Box E3)
    - Lucky--Get Lucky, red and white, undated (Box E3)
    - Magna--Magnatude, black, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Adventure Team, red, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Adventure Team gator, red and white, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Logo, red and white, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--"M" with rodeo horse, black, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Marlboro Unlimited, black, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Racing Team, black corduroy, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Racing Team, red, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Rodeo horse, black, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Red corduroy, undated (Box E3)
    - Marlboro--Red corduroy with piping, undated (Box E3)
    - Newport--High visibility green, undated (Box E3)
    - Newport--Newport Racing Team, white, undated (Box E3)
    - Newport--Newport Ski Spee, green corduroy, undated (Box E3)
    - Philip Morris--Logo, tan and gold, undated (Box E3)
    - Philip Morris--Logo, black and gold, undated (Box E3)
    - Players--Player's Ltd. Racing, two-tone blue, undated (Box E3)
    - R.J. Reynolds--The RJR Cup, white visor, undated (Box E4)
    - Rothmans--Logo, blue and white, undated (Box E4)
    - Salem--Green corduroy, undated (Box E4)
    - Salem--Salem SoundWaves, high visibility, undated (Box E4)
    - Salem--Salem Spirit, blue, undated (Box E4)